romancescam.com 2019-04-15

# Romance Scam - Privacy Policy

This page tells you how we use personal information collected at this website: [RomanceScam](https://www.romancescam.com/) Please read this privacy policy before using the website or submitting any personal information. By using the website, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology**  
We use cookies to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the website, and understanding how visitors use the website. Cookies can also help customize the website for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. 

Please read our full [Cookie Policy](https://www.romancescam.com/forum/app.php/page/cookie-policy)

**Information Collection and Use**

We collect personally identifiable information, like email address, only when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. This information is only used to sign you up for our service, for password recovery purposes and for sending you the site's important notifications, such as private message notifications. We do not collect real full names, addresses, phone numbers or any financial information such as credit card numbers from our users. We do not send out newsletters or any other promotional or marketing materials. Your information will be stored on our site until you choose to delete your account. 

**Information Sharing**

Romancescam website is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give to our site via registration form, email or other direct contact from you. We will never share your information with any third party outside of this website. We will never sell or rent this information to anyone.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**

a)You may opt out of any future contacts from Romancescam at any time. You may also opt out of any site's email notifications by editing your Site Preferences: under your username in navigation bar click on ["User Control Panel"](https://www.romancescam.com/forum/ucp.php) link.

b)You can change/correct any data we have about you any time by Editing your profile: under your username in navigation bar click on ["User Control Panel"](https://www.romancescam.com/forum/ucp.php) link.

c)You can delete your account and erase all information from our website completely. This is how:

\- If you registered directly through our registration form, you can delete your profile at any time by clicking on your username in navigation menu, then on ["User Control Panel"](https://www.romancescam.com/forum/ucp.php)", then on "Delete My Account" tab.

\- If you registered through a social network, like Facebook, you can request the administration to delete your profile by contacting us via [Contact page](https://www.romancescam.com/forum/app.php/contactadmin).

d)You can also contact us at any time via [Contact page](https://www.romancescam.com/forum/app.php/contactadmin) to see what data we have about you, if any, or express any concern you have about how we use your data.

**Security**

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information, that information is encrypted and transmitted to the site in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page. Only the owner of this site is granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

**Links**  
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that RomanceScam is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to beaware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

**Public Forums**  
This website contains public forums. Please remember that any information that you publish in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information in public forums. Always make sure you erase your name, email or any other personal identifiable information from your post.

**Private Messaging**

Members' private messages are stored in a database on the server, which can be accessed by the site administrators should the need arise, such as reports of spam or scam activity.

**IP addresses**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, prevent fraud, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact us via [Contact page](https://www.romancescam.com/forum/app.php/contactadmin)

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.  
This privacy policy was revised on May 24, 2018 for GDPR compliance.
